Guide to Raytheon Company Semiconductor Division Files Kept to Monitor the Electronics Industry, 1965-1986
Department of Special Collections
Raytheon Company Semiconductor Division Files Kept to Monitor the Electronics Industry,
1965-1986
M0661
Raytheon Company Semiconductor Division
11.5 linear ft.
Stanford University. Libraries. Dept. of Special Collections and University Archives.
The collection consists of files that Raytheon's Semiconductor Division kept to monitor both the progress of their competitors and trends in the electronics industry. The original organization of the files has been largely reproduced here. Gaps in the numerical filing system indicate that Raytheon chose to donate only selected files from its records.
Administrative Information
Access Restrictions
Consult Special Collections Staff.
Acquisition Information
Gift of San Jose Public Library, 1992.
Biography
Raytheon's Semiconductor Division was established in Mountain View, California in 1968 by its parent company, Raytheon Company of Lexington, Massachusetts, which, in 1990, was described as "one of the largest and most diversified electronics companies in the United States." In the early 1990s, the company was involved in the manufacture and distribution of semiconductors and had 1200 employees at its Mountain View location. In November of 1997, Raytheon sold its Semi-Conductors/Integrated Circuits Division to the Fairchild Semiconductor Corporation.
Collection Scope and Content Summary
The collection consists of files that Raytheon's Semiconductor Division kept to monitor both the progress of their competitors and trends in the electronics industry. The original organization of the files has been largely reproduced here. Gaps in the numerical filing system indicate that Raytheon chose to donate only selected files from its records. Overview of box contents: Boxes 1-17: Files numbered 1.0 through 17.18.1 (non-continuous) about electronics industry and market. Boxes 17-18: files on Raytheon itself. Box 19: other Raytheon research files (numbered R 5.6 and R 5.6A). Boxes 20-22: periodical articles. Box 23: seminars, magazines, educational materials.
Access Terms
The following terms have been used to index the description of this collection in the library's online public access catalog.
Little, Arthur D.; Advanced Memory Systems, Inc.; Advanced Micro Devices (Firm); American Micro Systems, Inc.; Ampex Corporation.; Analog Devices, Inc.; Autonetics.; Advanced LSI T ech., Inc.; Applied Materials.; Bell-Northern Research.; Cal Tex Semiconductor, Inc.; Cogar Corporation.; Collins Radio Company.; Computer Microtech, Inc.; Carter Semiconductor, Inc.; CTS Microelectronics, Inc.; Circuit Technology, Inc.; Data General Corporation.; Electronic Arrays, Inc.; Electronic Memories & Magnetics.; Energy Conversion Devices, Inc.; Exar Corporation.; Fairchild Camera and Instrument Corporation.; General Instrument Corporation.; Garrett Micro-Circuits Corporation.; Harris Semiconductor (Firm); Hughes Aircraft Company. Microelectronics Center.; Hugle International.; Harrison Intertype.; Halex.; International Business Machines Corporation.; ITT Corporation.; Inselek.; Interdesign, Inc.; Intersil, Inc.; Intel Corporation.; International Rectifier (Firm); Integrated Memories, Inc.; Kenics Electronics.; Litton Industries.; LSI Computer Systems.; Memory Tech., Inc.; Microma.; Microsystems International, Inc.; MOS Technology, Inc.; Monolithic Memories, Inc.; Mostek Corporation.; Motorola, Inc. Semiconductor Group.; Micro Power Systems, Inc.; Micro Mask.; National Cash Register Company.; National Semiconductor Corporation.; Nortec Electronics.; North American Microelectronics.; Nitron.; Optimized Technology.; Philco-Ford. Micro-Electronics Division.; Precision Monolithics Incorporated.; Qualidyne Corporation.; RCA Corporation. Solid State Division.; Ragen Semiconductor.; Reticon Corporation.; Semiconductor Electronic Memories, Inc.; Semicoa.; Signetics (Firm); Silicon General (Firm); Siliconix, Incorporated.; Solid State Devices, Inc.; Solitron Devices, Inc.; Sprague Electric Company.; Solid State Scientific, Inc.; Standard Resources Corporation.; Siemens Corporation.; Standard Microsystems Corporation.; Stewart-Warner Corporation.; Sylvania Electronics Systems.; Solid State Systems.; Texas Instruments Incorporated.; Teledyne Semiconductor (Mountain View, Calif.); Transition Electronic Corporation.; Tokyo Shibaura Electric Co.; Unisem Corporation.; Voradyne Semiconductor.; Viatron Computer Systems Corporation.; Western Digital Corporation.; Westinghouse Electric Company. Semiconductor Division.; Electronic industries.; Electronics--Research.; Microelectronics industry--California--Santa Clara County.; Science--History.
Collection Contents
- 1.0 Technologies (Box 1, Folder 1)
- 1.0 Technologies (Box 1, Folder 2)
- 1.0 Technologies (Box 1, Folder 3)
- 1.0 Technologies (Box 1, Folder 4)
- 1.0 Technologies (Box 1, Folder 5)
- 1.0 Technologies (Box 1, Folder 6)
- 1.0 Technologies (Box 1, Folder 7)
- 1.1 MOS (Box 2, Folder 1)
- 1.2 Bipolar (Box 2, Folder 2)
- 1.3 Amorphous (Box 2, Folder 3)
- 1.4 Memory (Box 2, Folder 4)
- 1.5 Hybrid (Box 2, Folder 5)
- 1.6 Microprocessor (Box 2, Folder 6)
- 2.0 Market Projections (Box 3, Folder 1)
- 2.0 Market Projections (Box 3, Folder 2)
- 2.1 MOS (Box 3, Folder 3)
- 2.2 Bipolar (Box 3, Folder 4)
- 2.2.1 DIC (Box 3, Folder 5)
- 2.2.2 LIC (Box 3, Folder 6)
- 2.3 Memories (Box 3, Folder 7)
- 2.4 Yield, Cost & Price (Box 3, Folder 8)
- 2.5 CATV (Box 3, Folder 9)
- 2.6 Hybrid (Box 3, Folder 10)
- 2.7 OEM (Box 3, Folder 11)
- 2.8 Optoelectronics (Box 3, Folder 12)
- 2.9 Discretes (Box 3, Folder 13)
- 3.0 Products & Applications (Box 4, Folder 1)
- 3.1 Systems Design Philosophy (Box 4, Folder 2)
- 3.2 Component Design (Box 4, Folder 3)
- 3.3 OEM Products (Box 4, Folder 4)
- 3.4 Consumer Electronics (Box 4, Folder 5)
- 4.0 Manufacturing (Box 4, Folder 6)
- 4.1 Material (Box 4, Folder 7)
- 4.2 Production (Box 4, Folder 8)
- 4.3 Equipment Technology (Box 4, Folder 9)
- 4.4 Product Assembly (empty in original!) (Box 4, Folder 10)
- 4.5 HI-REL (Box 4, Folder 11)
- 5.0 International (Box 4, Folder 12)
- 5.1 Britain (Box 4, Folder 13)
- 5.2 Europe (Box 4, Folder 14)
- 5.3 Asia (Box 4, Folder 15)
- 5.4 Canada (Box 4, Folder 16)
- 5.5 Mexico (Box 4, Folder 17)
- 5.6 Tarif (Box 4, Folder 18)
- 5.7 Japanese Technology (Box 4, Folder 19)
- 6.0 Semiconductor Industry (empty in original!) (Box 5, Folder 1)
- 6.1 History (Box 5, Folder 2)
- 6.1 History (Box 5, Folder 3)
- 6.1 History-- "Semiconductor Techonolgy through 1979" (Box 5, Folder 4)
- 6.1 History-- "Semiconductor Techonolgy through 1979" (Box 5, Folder 5)
- 6.1 History-- "Semiconductor Techonolgy through 1979" (Box 5, Folder 6)
- 6.2 Integrated Circuit Fundamentals (Box 5, Folder 7)
- 6.2 Integrated Circuit Fundamentals (Box 5, Folder 8)
- 6.2 Integrated Circuit Fundamentals (Box 5, Folder 9)
- 7.0 Competitors (Box 6, Folder 1)
- 7.1.1 Advanced Memory Systems, Inc. (AMS) (Box 6, Folder 2)
- 7.1.2 Advanced Micro Devices, Inc. (AMD) (Box 6, Folder 3)
- 7.1.3 American Micro-Systems, Inc. (AMI) (Box 6, Folder 4)
- 7.1.4 Ampex Corp. (Box 6, Folder 5)
- 7.1.5 Analog Devices, Inc. (Box 6, Folder 6)
- 7.1.6 Autonetics (Box 6, Folder 7)
- 7.1.7 Advanced LSI Tech., Inc. (Box 6, Folder 8)
- 7.1.8 Applied Materials (Box 6, Folder 9)
- 7.2.1 Bell-Northern Research Labs (Box 6, Folder 10)
- 7.3.1 Cal Tex Semiconductor, Inc. (Box 6, Folder 11)
- 7.3.2 Cogar Corp. (Box 6, Folder 12)
- 7.3.3 Collins Radio Co. (Box 6, Folder 13)
- 7.3.4 Computer Microtech, Inc. (CMI) (Box 6, Folder 14)
- 7.3.5 Carter Semiconductor, Inc. (Box 6, Folder 15)
- 7.3.6 CTS Nicroelectronics, Inc. (Box 6, Folder 16)
- 7.3.7 Circuit Technology, Inc. (Box 6, Folder 17)
- 7.4.1 Data General Corp. (Box 6, Folder 18)
- 7.5.0 Electronics Industry Financial(empty in original!) (Box 6, Folder 19)
- 7.5.1 Electronic Arrays, Inc. (EA) (Box 6, Folder 20)
- 7.5.2 Electronic Memories & Magnetics (EM & M) (Box 6, Folder 21)
- 7.5.3 Energy Conversion Devices, Inc. (ECD) (Box 6, Folder 22)
- 7.5.4 Exar Integrated Systems, Inc. (Box 6, Folder 23)
- 7.6.1 Fairchild Camera & Instrument Corp. (Box 7, Folder 1)
- 7.6.1 Fairchild Camera & Instrument Corp. (Box 7, Folder 2)
- 7.6.1 Fairchild Camera & Instrument Corp. (Box 7, Folder 3)
- 7.6.1 Fairchild Camera & Instrument Corp. (Box 7, Folder 4)
- 7.6.1 Fairchild Camera & Instrument Corp. (Box 7, Folder 5)
- 7.6.1 Fairchild Camera & Instrument Corp. (Box 7, Folder 6)
- 7.7.1 General Electric (Box 8, Folder 1)
- 7.7.2 General Instrument Corp. (Box 8, Folder 2)
- 7.7.3 Garrett Micro-Circuits Corp. (Box 8, Folder 3)
- 7.8.1 Harris Semiconductor Division (Box 8, Folder 4)
- 7.8.2 Hughes Microelectronics Division (Box 8, Folder 5)
- 7.8.3 Hugle International (Box 8, Folder 6)
- 7.8.4 Harrison Intertype (Box 8, Folder 7)
- 7.8.5 Halex (Box 8, Folder 8)
- 7.9.1 International Business Machines (IBM) (Box 8, Folder 9)
- 7.9.2 ITT Semiconductor (Box 8, Folder 10)
- 7.9.3 Inselek (Box 8, Folder 11)
- 7.9.4 Interdesign, Inc. (Box 8, Folder 12)
- 7.9.5 Intersil, Inc. (Box 8, Folder 13)
- 7.9.5 Intersil, Inc. (Box 8, Folder 14)
- 7.9.5 Intersil, Inc. (Box 8, Folder 15)
- 7.9.5 Intersil, Inc. (Box 8, Folder 16)
- 7.9.5 Intersil, Inc. (Box 8, Folder 17)
- 7.9.6 Intel Corporation (Box 9, Folder 1)
- 7.9.7 International Rectifier (Box 9, Folder 2)
- 7.9.8 Int. Isulated-Gate Technology, Inc. [sic] (original folder empty!) (Box 9, Folder 3)
- 7.9.9 Integrated Memories, Inc. (Box 9, Folder 4)
- 7.11.1 Kenics Electronics (Box 9, Folder 5)
- 7.12.1 Litton Systems, Inc. (Box 9, Folder 6)
- 7.12.2 LSI Computer Systems (Box 9, Folder 7)
- 7.13.1 Memory Tech., Inc. (Box 9, Folder 8)
- 7.13.2 Microma (Box 9, Folder 9)
- 7.13.3 Microsystems International, Inc. (MIL) (Box 9, Folder 10)
- 7.13.4 MOS Technology, Inc. (MOS) (Box 9, Folder 11)
- 7.13.5 Monolithic Memories, Inc. (MMI) (Box 9, Folder 12)
- 7.13.6 Mostek Corp. (Box 9, Folder 13)
- 7.13.7 Motorola Semiconductor (Box 9, Folder 14)
- 7.13.7 Motorola Semiconductor (Box 9, Folder 15)
- 7.13.7 Motorola Semiconductor (Box 9, Folder 16)
- 7.13.7 Motorola Semiconductor (Box 10, Folder 1)
- 7.13.8 Micro Power Systems, Inc. (Box 10, Folder 2)
- 7.13.9 Micro Mask (Box 10, Folder 3)
- 7.14.1 National Cash Register Co. (Box 10, Folder 4)
- 7.14.2 National Semiconductor Corp. (Box 10, Folder 5)
- 7.14.2 National Semiconductor Corp. (Box 10, Folder 6)
- 7.14.3 Nortec Electronics (Box 10, Folder 7)
- 7.14.4 North American Microelectronics (NRMEC) (Box 10, Folder 8)
- 7.14.5 Nitron (Box 10, Folder 9)
- 7.15.1 Optimized Technology (Box 10, Folder 10)
- 7.16.1 Philco-Ford Micro-Electronics Division (Box 10, Folder 11)
- 7.16.2 Precision Monolithics (Box 10, Folder 12)
- 7.17.1 Qualidyne Corp. (Box 10, Folder 13)
- 7.18.1 RCA Solid State Div. (Box 10, Folder 14)
- 7.18.2 Ragen Semiconductor (Box 10, Folder 15)
- 7.18.3 Raytheon Semiconductor Division (Box 11, Folder 1)
- 7.18.3 Raytheon Semiconductor Division (Box 11, Folder 2)
- 7.18.3 Raytheon Semiconductor Division (Box 11, Folder 3)
- 7.18.3 Raytheon Semiconductor Division (Box 11, Folder 4)
- 7.18.3 Raytheon Semiconductor Division (Box 11, Folder 5)
- 7.18.4 Reticon Corp. (Box 11, Folder 6)
- 7.19.1 (SEMI) Semiconductor Electronic Memories, Inc. (Box 11, Folder 7)
- 7.19.2 Semicoa (Box 11, Folder 8)
- 7.19.3 Signetics (Box 12, Folder 1)
- 7.19.3 Signetics (Box 12, Folder 2)
- 7.19.3 Signetics (Box 12, Folder 3)
- 7.19.3 Signetics (Box 12, Folder 4)
- 7.19.3 Signetics (Box 12, Folder 5)
- 7.19.3 Signetics (Box 12, Folder 6)
- 7.19.3 Signetics (Box 12, Folder 7)
- 7.19.5 Silicon General, Inc. (Box 12, Folder 8)
- 7.19.6 Siliconix, Inc. (Box 13, Folder 1)
- 7.19.8 Solid State Devices, Inc. (SSDI) (Box 13, Folder 2)
- 7.19.9 Solitron Devices, Inc. (Box 13, Folder 3)
- 7.19.10 Sprague Electric Co. (Box 13, Folder 4)
- 7.19.11Solid State Scientific, Inc. (Box 13, Folder 5)
- 7.19.12Standard Resources Corp. (Box 13, Folder 6)
- 7.19.13Siemens Corp. (Box 13, Folder 7)
- 7.19.14Standard Microsystems Corp. (Box 13, Folder 8)
- 7.19.15Stewart-Warner Corp. (Box 13, Folder 9)
- 7.19.16Sylvania (Box 13, Folder 10)
- 7.19.16Sylvania-- SUHL Spec (Box 13, Folder 11)
- 7.19.17Solid State Systems (Box 13, Folder 12)
- 7.20.1 Texas Instruments (Box 14, Folder 1)
- 7.20.1Texas Instruments (Box 14, Folder 2)
- 7.20.1Texas Instruments (Box 14, Folder 3)
- 7.20.1Texas Instruments (Box 14, Folder 4)
- 7.20.1Texas Instruments (Box 14, Folder 5)
- 7.20.1Texas Instruments Integrated Circuits Catalog, 1967-8 (Box 14, Volume 1)
- 7.20.2 Teledyne Semiconductor (Box 15, Folder 1)
- 7.20.3 Transition Electronic Corp. (Box 15, Folder 2)
- 7.20.4 Tokyo Shibaura Elec. Co. (Box 15, Folder 3)
- 7.21.1 Unisem Corp. (Box 15, Folder 4)
- 7.22.1 Voradyne Semiconductor (Box 15, Folder 5)
- Market (Box 15, Folder 6)
- 7.22.2 Viatron Computer Systems Corp. (Box 15, Folder 7)
- 7.23.1 Western Digital Corp. (Box 15, Folder 8)
- 7.23.2 Westinghouse Elec. Co., Semiconductor Division (Box 15, Folder 9)
- 8.3 National CBS (Box 15, Folder 10)
- 8.11 Graham & James (Box 15, Folder 11)
- 9.0 Consultants & Reference (Box 15, Folder 12)
- 9.1 Arthur D. Little (ADL) (Box 15, Folder 13)
- 9.1 Arthur D. Little (ADL) (Box 15, Folder 14)
- 9.1 Arthur D. Little (ADL) (Box 15, Folder 15)
- 9.2 Stanford Research Institute (Box 15, Folder 16)
- 9.3 Darling & Alsobrook (Box 15, Folder 17)
- 9.4 Bank of America (Box 15, Folder 18)
- 9.6 Mackintosh Consultants (Box 15, Folder 19)
- 9.7 Education Program (Box 16, Folder 1)
- 9.8 William D. Witter, Inc. (original folder empty!) (Box 16, Folder 2)
- 9.10 D.A.T.A., Inc. (Box 16, Folder 3)
- 9.12 Legal Reference (Box 16, Folder 4)
- 9.13 Foreign Tax Law (Box 16, Folder 5)
- 9.14 Electronic Industries Association (EIA) (Box 16, Folder 6)
- 9.15 Dataquest (Box 16, Folder 7)
- 9.15 Dataquest Semiconductor Procurement Conference, February 1986 (Box 16, Folder 8)
- 9.17 Gnostic Concepts (Box 16, Folder 9)
- 9.18 Integrated Circuits Engineering (ICE) (Box 16, Folder 10)
- 9.19 Stanford Electronic Laboratories (SEL) (Box 16, Folder 11)
- 9.20 Morgan Stanley Electronics Letter (Box 16, Folder 12)
- 9.21 Frost & Sullivan (Box 16, Folder 13)
- 9.22 Information Services (Index) (Box 16, Folder 14)
- 9.23 Loeb Rhoadez (Box 16, Folder 15)
- 9.24 FTC Report on the Semiconductor Industry(original) (Box 16, Folder 16)
- 9.24 FTC Report on the Semiconductor Industry (Box 16, Folder 17)
- 9.25 Research Institute of America (Box 17, Folder 1)
- 9.26 Semiconductor Industry Association (SIA) (Box 17, Folder 2)
- 9.27 Hoefler Newsletter (Box 17, Folder 3)
- 9.28 Santa Clara County Employment Report (Box 17, Folder 4)
- 13.03 Business/Economic Projections (Box 17, Folder 5)
- 13.04 Raytheon Company Statistics (Box 17, Folder 6)
- 17.5.1 Electronic Firms (Box 17, Folder 7)
- 17.5.1 Electronic Firms (Box 17, Folder 8)
- 17.5.1 Electronic Firms (Box 17, Folder 9)
- 17.18.1 Raytheon (Box 17, Folder 10)
- Raytheon-- Annual Reports (Box 17, Folder 11)
- Raytheon-- Company Brochures (Box 17, Folder 12)
- Raytheon-- Digital Product Newsletter (Box 18, Folder 1)
- Raytheon-- Electronic Progress (Box 18, Folder 2)
- Raytheon-- 54R/74R Series (Box 18, Folder 3)
- Raytheon-- Integrated Circuits (Box 18, Folder 4)
- Raytheon-- Linear Integrated Circuits (Box 18, Volume 1)
- Raytheon-- Microcomputer Components (Box 18, Folder 5)
- Raytheon-- Product Selection Guides (Box 18, Folder 6)
- Raytheon-- Product Specifications, 1965-69 (Box 18, Folder 7)
- Raytheon-- Product Specification, 1980-81 (Box 18, Folder 8)
- Raytheon-- PTS 100 General System Description (Box 18, Folder 9)
- Raytheon-- Raytheon Magazine (Box 18, Folder 10)
- Raytheon-- RLA 120 Linear Array Design Manual (Box 18, Folder 11)
- Raytheon-- Charles C. Wu & Randy Brandt, "Application of a Monolithic Dual High Gain Differential Amplifier," 1969. (Box 18, Folder 12)
- R5.6 (Box 19, Folder 1)
- R5.6 (Box 19, Folder 2)
- R5.6 A (Box 19, Folder 3)
- R5.6 A (Box 19, Folder 4)
- R5.6 A (Box 19, Folder 5)
- Semiconductor Industry Association (SIA), 1986 (Box 19, Folder 6)
- SIA (Box 19, Folder 7)
- U.S. Dept. of Commerce, "A Competitive Assessment of the U.S. Semiconductor Manufacturing Equipment Industry." (Box 19, Folder 8)
- American Electronics Association Update (Box 20, Folder 1)
- Business Week (Box 20, Folder 2)
- BWI Monthly (Box 20, Folder 3)
- California Business (Box 20, Folder 4)
- Circuits Manufacturing (Box 20, Folder 5)
- Computer Design (Box 20, Folder 6)
- Computer Decisions (Box 20, Folder 7)
- Computer Retailing (Box 20, Folder 8)
- Computerworld (Box 20, Folder 9)
- Computerworld (Box 20, Folder 10)
- Computerworld (Box 20, Folder 11)
- Computer Decisions (Box 20, Folder 12)
- Corporate Times (Box 20, Folder 13)
- Data Processor (Box 20, Folder 14)
- Dataguest (Box 20, Folder 15)
- Defense Electronics (Box 20, Folder 16)
- Datamation (Box 20, Folder 17)
- Datamation (Box 21, Folder 1)
- Digital Design (Box 21, Folder 2)
- Dun's Review (Box 21, Folder 3)
- Electronic Business (Box 21, Folder 4)
- Electronic Design (Box 21, Folder 5)
- Electronic News (Box 21, Folder 6)
- Electronic News (Box 21, Folder 7)
- Electronic News (Box 21, Folder 8)
- Electronic Products Magazine (Box 21, Folder 9)
- Electronics (Box 21, Folder 10)
- Electronics (Box 21, Folder 11)
- Electronics Letter (Box 21, Folder 12)
- Electronics Week (Box 21, Folder 13)
- Financial World (Box 21, Folder 14)
- Forbes (Box 21, Folder 15)
- The Futurist (Box 21, Folder 16)
- Harvard Business Review (Box 21, Folder 17)
- High Technology (Box 22, Folder 1)
- IBM Computing Report (Box 22, Folder 2)
- ICP Interface Small Business Management (Box 22, Folder 3)
- Information (Box 22, Folder 4)
- Industry Week (Box 22, Folder 5)
- Infosvstems (Box 22, Folder 6)
- Infosystems (Box 22, Folder 7)
- Minicomputer News (Box 22, Folder 8)
- Modern Office Procedures (Box 22, Folder 9)
- Mini-Micro Systems (Box 22, Folder 10)
- RELease 1.0 (formerly The Rosen Electronics Letter) (Box 22, Folder 11)
- RELease 1.0 (formerly The Rosen Electronics Letter) (Box 22, Folder 12)
- San Francisco Business Journal (Box 22, Folder 13)
- San Jose Business Journal (Box 22, Folder 14)
- Semiconductor International (Box 22, Folder 15)
- SIBS (Semiconductor Industry and Business Survey) (Box 22, Folder 16)
- Small Business Report (Box 22, Folder 17)
- Small Systems World (Box 22, Folder 18)
- Time (Box 22, Folder 19)
- University of Michigan Business Review (Box 22, Folder 20)
- VLSI Design (Box 22, Folder 21)
- Wall Street Journal (Box 22, Folder 22)
- The Wharton Magazine (Box 22, Folder 23)
- Articles from Unnamed Periodicals (Box 22, Folder 24)
- Seminars, Magazines, Educational Materials, 1975-76. (Box 23, Folder 1)
- Seminars, Magazines, Educational Materials, 1977. (Box 23, Folder 2)
- Seminars, Magazines, Educational Materials, 1978. (Box 23, Folder 3)
- Seminars, Magazines, Educational Materials, 1979. (Box 23, Folder 4)
- Seminars, Magazines, Educational Materials, 1980. (Box 23, Folder 5)
- Seminars, Magazines, Educational Materials, undated. (Box 23, Folder 6)